Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Interviews
  - The South Central Michigan QSOS
    - Rosemary Kimball oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-03-21 (Interview-id MI49016-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_008_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_008_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_008_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_MI49016_008_01.wav; afc2007009_MI49016_008_02.wav
    - Estella Spates oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2010-02-12 (Interview-id MI49016-009)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_009_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_009_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_009_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_009_04.wav
    - Rosie Bond oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2010-02-15 (Interview-id MI49016-010)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_010_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_010_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_010_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_010_04.wav
    - Harriett DeRose oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2010-02-16 (Interview-id MI49016-011)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_011_02.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_011_03.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_011_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_011_01.wav
    - Kay Horton oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-03-29 (Interview-id MI49016-012)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_012_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_012_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_012_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_012_04.wav
    - Carol Miller oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2010-05-19 (Interview-id MI49016-013)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_013_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_013_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_013_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_013_04.wav
    - Lyn Brown oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-04-08 (Interview-id MI49016-014)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_014_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_014_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_014_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_014_04.wav
    - Dorothy Weeks oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-09-10 (Interview-id MI49016-015)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_015_01.docx; afc2007009_MI49016_015_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_015_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_015_04.wav
    - Shirlee Burlingame oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2010-06-10 (Interview-id MI49016-016)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_016_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_016_03.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_016_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_016_02.wav
    - Jean Champagne oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-02-10 (Interview-id MI49016-017)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_017_02.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_017_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_017_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_017_04.wav
    - Jean Sadowski Pufpaff oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-03-04 (Interview-id MI49016-018)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_018_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_018_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_018_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_018_04.wav
    - Eleanor Wilkinson oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-05-03 (Interview-id MI49016-019)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_019_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_019_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_019_03.tif
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_019_04.wav
    - Joyce S. Rupp oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2010-06-11 (Interview-id MI49016-020)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_020_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_020_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_020_03.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_020_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_020_05.wav
    - Juanita Kohfeldt oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2010-07-01 (Interview-id MI49016-021)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_021_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_021_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_021_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_021_01.wav
    - Wanda Warner oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2010-07-26 (Interview-id MI49016-022)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_022_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_022_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_022_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_022_04.wav
    - Linda Uldriks oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2010-07-20 (Interview-id MI49016-023)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_023_02.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_023_03.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_023_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_023_01.wav
    - Dale Waddle oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2010-07-29 (Interview-id MI49016-024)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_024_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_024_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_024_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_024_04.wav
    - Barbara Miller oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2010-09-22 (Interview-id MI49016-025)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_025_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_025_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_025_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_025_04.wav
    - Barbara Mason oral history interview conducted by Estella Spates, 2009-05-16 (Interview-id MI49016-026)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_026_02.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_026_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_026_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_026_04.wav
    - Shirley Wilson oral history interview conducted by Joyce Rupp, 2011-10-12 (Interview-id MI49016-027)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_027_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_027_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_027_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_027_04.wav
    - Charlotte C. (Bishop) Egan oral history interview conducted by Joyce Rupp, 2011-07-07 (Interview-id MI49016-028)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_028_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_028_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_028_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_028_04.wav
    - June Harman Swartzle oral history interview conducted by Joyce Rupp, 2011-08-19 (Interview-id MI49016-029)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_029_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_029_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_029_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_029_04.wav
    - Winifred Rombaugh oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2010-11-16 (Interview-id MI49016-032)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_032_02.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_032_03.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_032_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_032_01.wav
    - Janis Ludwig oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-02-09 (Interview-id MI49016-033)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_033_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_033_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_033_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_033_04.wav
    - Marian Daniel oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-02-18 (Interview-id MI49016-034)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_034_04.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_034_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_034_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_034_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_034_05.wav
    - Irene Gilbert oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-03-04 (Interview-id MI49016-035)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_035_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_035_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_035_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_035_04.wav
    - Gail Rayman oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-03-11 (Interview-id MI49016-036)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 2 digital documents, 4 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_036_02.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_036_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_036_04-07.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_036_01.wav
    - Shirley Fuller oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-03-11 (Interview-id MI49016-037)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_037_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_037_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_037_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_037_04.wav
    - Lori Smith oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-03-18 (Interview-id MI49016-038)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_038_02.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_038_03.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_038_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_038_01.wav
    - Terry Doty oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-03-18 (Interview-id MI49016-039)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_039_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_039_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_039_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_039_04.wav
    - Beth Payne-Howard oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-03-25 (Interview-id MI49016-040)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_040_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_040_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_040_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_040_04.wav
    - Joyce Ashley oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-03-25 (Interview-id MI49016-041)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_041_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_041_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_041_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_041_04.wav
    - Nancy Everling oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-03-28 (Interview-id MI49016-042)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_042_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_042_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_042_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_042_04.wav
    - Barbara Williams oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-04-10 (Interview-id MI49016-043)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_043_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_043_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_043_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_043_04.wav
    - Marcia Lippen oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-04-01 (Interview-id MI49016-044)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_044_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_044_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_044_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_044_04.wav
    - Mary DuBois oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-04-01 (Interview-id MI49016-045)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_045_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_045_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_045_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_045_04.wav
    - Pam Schultz oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-05-16 (Interview-id MI49016-047)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_047_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_047_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_047_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_047_04.wav
    - Cynthia Mumford oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-05-24 (Interview-id MI49016-048)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_048_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_048_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_048_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_048_04.wav
    - Mary Jo Bundy oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-06-13 (Interview-id MI49016-049)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_049_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_049_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_049_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_049_04.wav
    - Dorothy M. DePouw Naegele oral history interview conducted by Joyce Rupp, 2011-08-24 (Interview-id MI49016-053)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_053_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_053_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_053_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_053_04.wav
    - Sharon K. Naegele Eshlaman oral history interview conducted by Joyce Rupp, 2011-08-31 (Interview-id MI49016-054)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_054_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_054_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_054_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_054_04.wav
    - Arveda Jean Yeo oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-09-10 (Interview-id MI49016-058)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_058_01.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_058_02.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_058_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_058_04.cda
    - Susan Jorena oral history interview conducted by Eleanor Wilkinson, 2011-09-11 (Interview-id MI49016-060)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_060_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_060_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_060_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_060_04.wav
    - Mary Hill oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-10-08 (Interview-id MI49016-061)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_061_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_061_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_061_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_061_04.wav
    - Salinda Ash oral history interview conducted by Pam Schultz, 2011-09-10 (Interview-id MI49016-062)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MI49016_062_03.doc; afc2007009_MI49016_062_01.jpg; afc2007009_MI49016_062_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_MI49016_062_04.wav
  - The South Dakota QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in South Dakota.
    - Judy Haas oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-09-24 (Interview-id SD57744-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_SD57744_001_07.rtf; afc2007009_SD57744_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_SD57744_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_SD57744_001_03.wav; afc2007009_SD57744_001_05.wav
  - The Tennessee QSOS
    - Unidentified Interview(s) (Interview-id TN38555-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 17 4x6 color prints
  - The Texas QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Texas.
    - Leisa Rich oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-06-18 (Interview-id TX75019-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Lissa Alexander oral history interview conducted by Amy Milne, 2011-03-05 (Interview-id TX75234-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_TX75234_001_01.docx; afc2007009_TX75234_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_TX75234_001_04.jpg; afc2007009_TX75234_001_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_TX75234_001_02.wav
    - Carol Florance oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2003-09-20 (Interview-id TX76073-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR612
    - Richard Tims oral history interview conducted by Meg Cox, 2010-03-21 (Interview-id TX76308-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_TX76308_001_01.doc; afc2007009_TX76308_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_TX76308_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_TX76308_001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_TX76308_001_05.wav
    - Spike Gillespie oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-06-23 (Interview-id TX78765-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_TX78765_001_04.doc; afc2007009_TX78765_001_01.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_TX78765_001_02.wav
  - The Trinity Valley Quilters' Guild QSOS
    QSOS volunteers from the Trinity Valley Quilters' Guild conducted interviews with members of their guild before and during their annual 2001 and 2002 Quiltfest in Fort Worth, Texas. This project was initiated by QSOS volunteers Kay and Paul Jones.
    - Beatrice Schmidtzinsky oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-03-15 (Interview-id TX76121-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Jean Vining oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-03-15 (Interview-id TX76121-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR170
    - Alice Robinson oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-03-15 (Interview-id TX76121-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR171
    - Jerene Dorsey oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-03-15 (Interview-id TX76121-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Peggy Burns oral history interview conducted by Jane Kucko, 2001-03-15 (Interview-id TX76121-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Martha Austin oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-03-16 (Interview-id TX76121-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Dixie Heath oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-03-16 (Interview-id TX76121-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR172
    - Nannie Don Northcutt oral history interview, 2001-03-16 (Interview-id TX76121-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR173
    - Helen West oral history interview conducted by Jane Kucko, 2001-03-17 (Interview-id TX76121-009)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Mary Sue Simpson oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-03-17 (Interview-id TX76121-010)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Peggy Mayfield oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-03-17 (Interview-id TX76121-011)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Joanie Grimm oral history interview conducted by Jane Kucko, 2001-03-17 (Interview-id TX76121-012)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR174
    - Sandra McCartney oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-04-20 (Interview-id TX76121-013)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Jean Thompson oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-014)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Polly Powell oral history interview conducted by Jane Kucko, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-015)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR175
    - Josephine Grimes oral history interview conducted by Edie Jones, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-016)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR176
    - Charles Wunderlich oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-017)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Ann Box oral history interview conducted by Jane Kucko, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-018)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Nancy Deen oral history interview conducted by Mimi Ayars, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-019)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Nancy Chick oral history interview conducted by Jane Kucko, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-020)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Susan Deal oral history interview conducted by Mimi Ayars, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-022)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR177
    - Jan Hair oral history interview conducted by Edie Jones, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-023)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Jayne Naff oral history interview conducted by Jane Kucko, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-024)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Sondra Williams oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-05-18 (Interview-id TX76121-025)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Kathryn Anderson oral history interview conducted by Kay Jones, 2001-05-19 (Interview-id TX76121-026)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Iris Young oral history interview conducted by Judy Linn, 2001-05-19 (Interview-id TX76121-027)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Glennis Bradley oral history interview conducted by Cary Shields, 2001-05-19 (Interview-id TX76121-028)